GIULIA KARANXHA

Barcelona, 08860 | +34 611505903 karanxhagiuliawork@gmail.com | https://karanxhagiulia.github.io

Summary

I like simplifying complex information through data to drive positive change within a business. I have strong technical skills in SQL, Excel, Power BI/Tableau, Power Automate, and Python, and I use them to extract, analyze, and present data through **dashboards** and **presentations**. In addition to my ongoing studies for a Bachelor of **Business Administration in IT** from Laurea University, I have experience managing medium-sized groups (30 people) and creating documentation in the workplace. My background in customer service, focusing on people management and project management, has also equipped me with strong communication and interpersonal skills. Fluent in **English**, **Italian**, **Spanish** (intermediate), and **French** (basic), I lived in Australia from 2018 to 2021.

Skills

Expert in: **Excel, Canva, PowerPoint**, communication and creating clear documentation, people management

Intermediate in: Python, SQL, HTML & CSS, Tableau, PowerBI, Power Automate, Figma

Basic in: Linux (Bash), BigQuery, Google Cloud, MySQL, SQL Server, Git, Java, d3.js, MS SharePoint

Education

B.B.A (Business Administration) in IT

2022-2024 (Expected)

Laurea University of Applied Sciences, Online Specialization: Developing Digital Services.

Business, project management, marketing and digital marketing, network, Agile/DevOps frameworks.

Tech: HTML, CSS, Python, Linux, Java, UX/UI, Web Design, QA testing. Grades: 4.7/5

EQF Level 4 Diploma as Data Analyst

2021-2022

IFOA, Bologna (Italy)

- Maths & Statistics
 - Data mining and text with Spacy, NLKT, NooJ
 - ML, Python libraries (Sci-kit Learn, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly)

Experience

SPS Associate May 2022 - Dec 2022

Amazon, Barcelona, Remote

- Project owner for the NVA tickets (non-value-added) of my team. I reduced the average of NVA from 26% to a steady 7% (well under the 10% target) in 7 weeks by coaching other associates through presentations, analysis, and finding defects in the processes;
- Launched the use of **Asana** (project management tool) in the team
- Created supporting Quip documentation for the team and weekly reports to my manager;
- Created tickets to improve and update the current SOP;
- Mentored my colleagues to improve their performance acting as a point of contact;
- Provided timely and accurate operational support to Merchants selling on the Amazon platform by chat, e-mail, and phone contacts.
- Kept my performance in the top 20%.

Store Manager 2017 - 2018

CeX Webuy.com, Parma, Bologna, Italy

New opening in Parma, 4th store for CeX (Webuy.com) in Italy.

I spent the last months working in all four Italian shops, living in Bologna, in an international environment. This job helped me to get a strong management background in a retail environment.

- My store consistently scored **over 85%** in the monthly OPS report
- In the last two years, Trustpilot's score of our Country **increased by almost 3 points**, ranking Italy in first place among all CeX stores in the world for e-commerce customer satisfaction;
- Initiate changes to improve the business based on the data available, e.g. revising Sundays opening hours to ensure the store can compete effectively in the local market, becoming the first store in Italy with different opening hours on Sundays.

Deputy Store Manager

Feb 2017 - August 2017

KASANOVA, Parma, Italy

New opening for a home furnishing retail store.

- Strengthened the technology skills of my colleagues, training them to use the company's software;
- Managed a team of 7, arranging the timetables;
- Created the Facebook page building up customer loyalty to the brand.

Volunteer

School Teacher, Nairobi, Kenya EVS

Dec 2016 - Jan 2017

Red Cross Volunteer, Italy

2011-2015

Links

GitHub: https://github.com/karanxhagiulia

Tableau: https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/karanxhagiulia

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/karanxhagiulia/

Certifications

Applied Data Science with Python - Level 2, IBM Cognitive Class Introduction to Cybersecurity, CISCO

Languages

English C2

Italian C2

Spanish B1-B2 (Completely understand it, but still learning the correct grammar to speak it!)

French B1 Finnish A1